{"sourceUrl": "https://newsroom.clevelandclinic.org/2020/03/18/frequently-asked-questions-about-coronavirus-disease-2019-covid-19/", "sourceName": "Cleveland Clinic", "dateScraped": 1584976955.265823, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1584894600.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "1f7684fe-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "answerUUID": "1f768684-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "exampleUUID": "1f768742-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "questionText": "What is COVID-19?", "answerText": "COVID-19 is a virus strain, first identified in Wuhan, Hubei Province, China, that has only spread in people since December 2019.\nHealth experts are closely monitoring the situation because little is known about this new virus and it has the potential to cause severe illness and pneumonia in some people.", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://newsroom.clevelandclinic.org/2020/03/18/frequently-asked-questions-about-coronavirus-disease-2019-covid-19/", "sourceName": "Cleveland Clinic", "dateScraped": 1584976955.266043, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1584894600.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "1f76883c-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "answerUUID": "1f7688f0-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "exampleUUID": "1f768990-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "questionText": "How does COVID-19 spread and what are the symptoms?", "answerText": "COVID-19 is primarily spread through respiratory droplets. That means to become infected, you generally must be within six feet of someone who is contagious and come into contact with these droplets. It may be possible to get COVID-19 by touching a surface or object that has the virus on it and then touching your mouth, nose, or possibly their eyes, Symptoms of COVID-19 appear within two to 14 days after exposure and include fever, cough, and shortness of breath.", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://newsroom.clevelandclinic.org/2020/03/18/frequently-asked-questions-about-coronavirus-disease-2019-covid-19/", "sourceName": "Cleveland Clinic", "dateScraped": 1584976955.2660985, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1584894600.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "1f768a58-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "answerUUID": "1f768b02-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "exampleUUID": "1f768bde-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "questionText": "How long does it take for symptoms of the COVID-19 to appear?", "answerText": "The CDC believes that symptoms of COVID-19 may appear in as few as two days, or as long as 14 days after exposure.", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://newsroom.clevelandclinic.org/2020/03/18/frequently-asked-questions-about-coronavirus-disease-2019-covid-19/", "sourceName": "Cleveland Clinic", "dateScraped": 1584976955.2661579, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1584894600.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "1f768cb0-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "answerUUID": "1f768d5a-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "exampleUUID": "1f768dfa-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "questionText": "How is COVID-19 treated?", "answerText": "There is currently no FDA approved medication for COVID-19. People infected with this virus should receive supportive care such as rest, fluids and fever control, to help relieve symptoms. For severe cases, treatment should include care to support vital organ functions.\nPrevention", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://newsroom.clevelandclinic.org/2020/03/18/frequently-asked-questions-about-coronavirus-disease-2019-covid-19/", "sourceName": "Cleveland Clinic", "dateScraped": 1584976955.2662103, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1584894600.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "1f768eae-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "answerUUID": "1f768f58-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "exampleUUID": "1f768ff8-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "questionText": "Is there a vaccine?", "answerText": "Currently, there is no vaccine available.", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://newsroom.clevelandclinic.org/2020/03/18/frequently-asked-questions-about-coronavirus-disease-2019-covid-19/", "sourceName": "Cleveland Clinic", "dateScraped": 1584976955.2662618, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1584894600.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "1f7690de-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "answerUUID": "1f769192-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "exampleUUID": "1f769232-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "questionText": "How can I best protect myself?", "answerText": "Practice the following:\nWash your hands often with soap and water for at least 15-20 seconds. If soap and water are not available, use a hand sanitizer with at least 60% alcohol.\nAvoid touching your eyes, nose and mouth with unwashed hands.\nAvoid close contact (within 6 feet) with people who are sick.\nStay home when you are sick.\nCover your cough or sneeze with a tissue, then throw the tissue in the trash.\nStandard household cleansers and wipes are effective in cleaning and disinfecting frequently touched objects and surfaces.\nIt’s currently flu and respiratory disease season and CDC recommends getting vaccinated, taking everyday preventive actions to stop the spread of germs, and taking flu antivirals if prescribed.", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://newsroom.clevelandclinic.org/2020/03/18/frequently-asked-questions-about-coronavirus-disease-2019-covid-19/", "sourceName": "Cleveland Clinic", "dateScraped": 1584976955.2663188, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1584894600.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "1f7692fa-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "answerUUID": "1f7693a4-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "exampleUUID": "1f769462-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "questionText": "Should I wear a face mask? Will that help protect me?", "answerText": "If you are sick: You should wear a facemask when you are around other people (like sharing a room or vehicle) and before you enter a healthcare provider’s office. If you are not able to wear a facemask (for example, because it causes trouble breathing), then you should do your best to cover your coughs and sneezes, and people who are caring for you should wear a facemask if they enter your room. Learn what to do if you are sick.\nIf you are not sick: You do not need to wear a facemask unless you are caring for someone who is sick (and they are not able to wear a facemask). Facemasks may be in short supply and they should be saved for caregivers.\n\n\nAccess and Visitor Restrictions in Ohio Locations", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://newsroom.clevelandclinic.org/2020/03/18/frequently-asked-questions-about-coronavirus-disease-2019-covid-19/", "sourceName": "Cleveland Clinic", "dateScraped": 1584976955.2663748, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1584894600.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "1f76952a-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "answerUUID": "1f7695d4-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "exampleUUID": "1f769674-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "questionText": "I have an appointment at Cleveland Clinic and I am concerned about COVID-19. Should I cancel my appointment?", "answerText": "We are taking necessary precautions on behalf of our patients, visitors and caregivers.\nAt this time our primary care providers are reviewing patient records and encouraging all of our Ohio patients with non-essential primary care appointments scheduled to take place in the next few weeks to consider rescheduling for three months out.\nFor appointments that cannot be postponed, options will include Cleveland Clinic Express Care® Online, phone and MyChart visits, with in-person appointments being a back-up option.\nFor patients who require a physical exam, in-person appointments will remain as scheduled.  We are closely monitoring this evolving situation and our clinicians are meeting regularly to continue to prepare.\nIf you have a fever, cough or shortness of breath, or are otherwise concerned you have COVID-19, we ask that you do not come to any Cleveland Clinic facility without calling your primary care physician or speaking to a provider using a virtual visit using Cleveland Clinic Express Care® Online. Patients will then be evaluated to determine if they require being seen in person or if they meet CDC guidelines for testing for COVID-19 based on symptoms, travel and exposures. If a patient meets criteria for testing, their Express Care Online provider or primary care physician will advise how to proceed with testing.", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://newsroom.clevelandclinic.org/2020/03/18/frequently-asked-questions-about-coronavirus-disease-2019-covid-19/", "sourceName": "Cleveland Clinic", "dateScraped": 1584976955.266428, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1584894600.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "1f76973c-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "answerUUID": "1f7697e6-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "exampleUUID": "1f76987c-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "questionText": "Can I bring someone with me to my scheduled appointment?", "answerText": "For Ohio locations:\nAt this time, no guests or visitors are permitted to accompany adult patients, unless special assistance is required.\nPediatric patients, elderly patients and those with special needs are permitted to bring no more than one guest. No more than two guests will be permitted per family or group.\nVisitors who are sick, have a fever, or a confirmed case of COVID-19 should not visit or accompany a patient.\nVisitors must wash their hands (or use sanitizer) before and after entering clinical areas and waiting rooms.", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://newsroom.clevelandclinic.org/2020/03/18/frequently-asked-questions-about-coronavirus-disease-2019-covid-19/", "sourceName": "Cleveland Clinic", "dateScraped": 1584976955.2664802, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1584894600.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "1f769958-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "answerUUID": "1f769a02-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "exampleUUID": "1f769a98-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "questionText": "I have a surgery scheduled at Cleveland Clinic, will it be canceled?", "answerText": "Ohio:\nThe Ohio Governor’s office, in collaboration with the Ohio Hospital Association, announced new guidelines on postponing non-essential surgeries, a related procedures, for adult and pediatric patients.\nCleveland Clinic will use these guidelines to determine which procedures and surgeries should be postponed.\nPatients who have non-essential procedures scheduled between Thursday, March 19th and Friday, March 27th will be contacted by Cleveland Clinic.\nFlorida:\nCleveland Clinic Florida is using guidelines set by Centers for Medicare & Medicaid Services to determine which procedures are nonessential and should be postponed. Going forward, procedures must be lifesaving for the patient, preserving function of organs or limbs, reducing risk of metastasis or progression of disease, or reducing risk of severe symptoms.\nSurgical cases, such as, urgent or emergent surgery, cancer surgery or cancer evaluation, infected joints, or other indications consistent with the government guidelines will continue.\nExamples of nonessential surgeries and related procedures include deferrable bronchoscopy, deferrable upper and lower endoscopies, routine dental procedures, symptomatic problems which are stable, management of benign conditions, cosmetics, primary and revision joint therapy (non-infected), bariatric and elective hernia surgery, and urogynecology.\nThe relationships between our physicians and patients is an essential part of the care we provide, and we are relying on our clinicians to follow these guidelines and exercise their best professional judgment. If a physician and patient determine a procedure cannot be postponed, it may be performed.\nCleveland Clinic Florida has already begun to contact patients who have nonessential procedures scheduled to discuss next steps.", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://newsroom.clevelandclinic.org/2020/03/18/frequently-asked-questions-about-coronavirus-disease-2019-covid-19/", "sourceName": "Cleveland Clinic", "dateScraped": 1584976955.2665339, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1584894600.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "1f769b6a-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "answerUUID": "1f769c14-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "exampleUUID": "1f769cb4-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "questionText": "How have visiting hours changed at Cleveland Clinic because of COVID-19?", "answerText": "Inpatient Locations: For all hospital locations in Ohio and Florida, we are restricting all visitors.\nExceptions will be made for the following patients:\nPediatric patients (1 visitor)\nLabor & Delivery patients (1 visitor)\nEnd-of-life circumstances (patient’s care team will discuss with their family)\nAll other visitors will be asked to leave the hospital. As we continue to navigate the best ways to contain the spread of COVID-19, we understand these changes are difficult and appreciate your patience and understanding.\nOutpatient Locations: For all family health centers, medical office building and physician offices in Ohio and Florida, we are restricting visitors following these guidelines:\nAt this time, no guests or visitors are permitted to accompany adult patients, unless special assistance is required.\nPediatric patients, elderly patients and those with special needs are permitted to bring no more than one guest. No more than two guests will be permitted per family or group.\nVisitors who are sick, have a fever, or a confirmed case of COVID-19 should not visit or accompany a patient.\nVisitors must wash their hands (or use sanitizer) before and after entering clinical areas and waiting rooms.\nThese restrictions are being put in place for the safety of our patients, caregivers and community. Thank you for your understanding.", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://newsroom.clevelandclinic.org/2020/03/18/frequently-asked-questions-about-coronavirus-disease-2019-covid-19/", "sourceName": "Cleveland Clinic", "dateScraped": 1584976955.2665877, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1584894600.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "1f769d72-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "answerUUID": "1f769e12-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "exampleUUID": "1f769eb2-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "questionText": "I have an appointment at Cleveland Clinic. What do I need to bring?", "answerText": "When entering any Cleveland Clinic facility, please have your appointment reminder from email, MyChart or text message to show.\nOn-Site Testing for Ohio Locations", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://newsroom.clevelandclinic.org/2020/03/18/frequently-asked-questions-about-coronavirus-disease-2019-covid-19/", "sourceName": "Cleveland Clinic", "dateScraped": 1584976955.2666385, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1584894600.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "1f769f70-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "answerUUID": "1f76a01a-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "exampleUUID": "1f76a0ba-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "questionText": "Is there an online screening tool available?", "answerText": "Yes. Cleveland Clinic launched a free COVID-19 screening tool to find out your risk level based on symptoms and travel.\nFollow these steps:\nVisit ClevelandClinic.org\nClick “Start your screening now”\nA questionnaire window will open\nAnswer questions to receive your recommendations", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://newsroom.clevelandclinic.org/2020/03/18/frequently-asked-questions-about-coronavirus-disease-2019-covid-19/", "sourceName": "Cleveland Clinic", "dateScraped": 1584976955.2666903, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1584894600.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "1f76a178-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "answerUUID": "1f76a24a-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "exampleUUID": "1f76a2fe-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "questionText": "What patients are being prioritized for testing?", "answerText": "COVID-19 testing will focus on high-risk patients. These are symptomatic patients who also have one of the following criteria:\nPatients 61 & older\nPatients under 36 months\nOn immunosuppressive therapy\nCancer\nEnd-stage renal disease and are on dialysis\nDiabetes\nHypertension\nCoronary artery disease\nHeart failure reduced ejection fraction\nLung disease\nContact with a known COVID-19 patient\nHIV/AIDS\nSolid organ transplants\nThese patients will continue to be tested at the W.O. Walker testing facility with a Cleveland Clinic physician’s order.", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://newsroom.clevelandclinic.org/2020/03/18/frequently-asked-questions-about-coronavirus-disease-2019-covid-19/", "sourceName": "Cleveland Clinic", "dateScraped": 1584976955.2667494, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1584894600.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "1f76a3d0-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "answerUUID": "1f76a47a-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "exampleUUID": "1f76a51a-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "questionText": "What if I am not a high-risk patient and need to receive testing?", "answerText": "For patients 60 and under who already have a Cleveland Clinic physician’s order, we are re-evaluating our ability to provide COVID-19 testing and are asking they not report to the W.O. Walker testing facility until they are contacted by Cleveland Clinic with further instructions. We are advising patients with a fever higher than 100.4 degrees F and/or cough to please isolate themselves from others. If your medical condition worsens, please contact your primary care provider or go to the emergency department.", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://newsroom.clevelandclinic.org/2020/03/18/frequently-asked-questions-about-coronavirus-disease-2019-covid-19/", "sourceName": "Cleveland Clinic", "dateScraped": 1584976955.2668028, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1584894600.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "1f76a5ec-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "answerUUID": "1f76a696-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "exampleUUID": "1f76a736-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "questionText": "If I’m a candidate for testing, where should I go?", "answerText": "Ohio:\nOn-site drive-through testing for COVID-19 is located in the garage of the W.O. Walker Building on Cleveland Clinic’s main campus. Testing is open 11 a.m. – 5 p.m., seven days a week.\nPlease Note: A Cleveland Clinic electronic provider’s order is required for COVID-19 testing.\nDirections to Testing Location:\nW.O. Walker Building\n10524 Euclid Ave.\nCleveland, OH 44195\nPatients should enter the garage from E. 105th St.\nFlorida:\nOn-site testing is located at Martin North Hospital and Tradition Hospital for COVID-19 by appointment only. Testing is open 8 a.m. – 5 p.m., seven days a week.\nPlease Note: To receive an appointment, individuals who believe they may have symptoms of COVID-19 must first call a nurse triage hotline at 772.419.3360, between 8 a.m. – 5 p.m.\nOn-site testing is located at Indian River Hospital for COVID-19 by appointment only. Testing is open 9 a.m. – 5 p.m., seven days a week.\nPlease Note: To receive an appointment, individuals who believe they may have symptoms of COVID-19 must first call our nurse triage hotline at 772.226.4846 between 9 a.m. and 5 p.m.\nDirections to Testing Locations:\nMartin North Hospital\n200 SE Hospital Ave.\nStuart , Florida 34994\nTradition Hospital\n10000 SW Innovation Way\nPort St. Lucie , Florida 34987\nIndian River Hospital\n1000 36th Street\nVero Beach, Florida 32960", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://newsroom.clevelandclinic.org/2020/03/18/frequently-asked-questions-about-coronavirus-disease-2019-covid-19/", "sourceName": "Cleveland Clinic", "dateScraped": 1584976955.2668562, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1584894600.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "1f76a7f4-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "answerUUID": "1f76a894-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "exampleUUID": "1f76a934-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "questionText": "How long will results from a COVID-19 test take?", "answerText": "Cleveland Clinic’s on-site testing should yield results within one day and testing results will be automatically released through MyChart within 5 days.", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://newsroom.clevelandclinic.org/2020/03/18/frequently-asked-questions-about-coronavirus-disease-2019-covid-19/", "sourceName": "Cleveland Clinic", "dateScraped": 1584976955.266908, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1584894600.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "1f76a9fc-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "answerUUID": "1f76aaa6-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "exampleUUID": "1f76ab46-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "questionText": "What do I do if I have flu-like symptoms and think I have been exposed to COVID-19?", "answerText": "Based on your symptoms, do the following:\nIf you’re concerned you have COVID-19, we recommend you start with a virtual visit using Cleveland Clinic Express Care® Online, an eVisit questionnaire in MyChart*, or call or message your primary care physician. You will be advised what to do next.\nCall ahead before going in person to any Cleveland Clinic location.\nIf you have chest pain, shortness of breath, dizziness, a severe headache or other potentially life-threatening problems, go to the nearest emergency department or call 911.\nFor questions, Call Ohio Department of Health’s 24/7 hotline at 833.4.ASK.ODH.\nCleveland Clinic patients call 855.697.3750.* For eVisits: Patients must be a current MyChart user and in the state of Ohio. After completing a questionnaire, Cleveland Clinic providers will review your submitted answers and evaluate your illness. If the provider suspects you may be infected with COVID-19, they will determine the most appropriate place to send you for testing, ensure you get the right care and minimize spread.", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://newsroom.clevelandclinic.org/2020/03/18/frequently-asked-questions-about-coronavirus-disease-2019-covid-19/", "sourceName": "Cleveland Clinic", "dateScraped": 1584976955.2669632, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1584894600.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "1f76ac2c-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "answerUUID": "1f76ace0-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "exampleUUID": "1f76ad80-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "questionText": "Who is screening patients?", "answerText": "We are following CDC recommendations on screening for travel from high-risk countries. As part of the intake process, travel questions have been added to outpatient visits. Travel screenings are part of the standard process for inpatients.\nScreening is occurring in the following ways:\nTravel screening is now performed at check-in, registration and during scheduling.\nIt has also been added to the outpatient rooming and inpatient admissions workflows.\nClinicians in Emergency Departments, labor and delivery and surgical areas will continue to complete travel screenings as a part of their standard workflows.\nThese questions are also asked at check-in kiosks and through MyChart’s pre-check-in feature.\nIn our intensive care units for patients with severe lower respiratory infections.\nPreparedness", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://newsroom.clevelandclinic.org/2020/03/18/frequently-asked-questions-about-coronavirus-disease-2019-covid-19/", "sourceName": "Cleveland Clinic", "dateScraped": 1584976955.2670178, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1584894600.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "1f76ae3e-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "answerUUID": "1f76aee8-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "exampleUUID": "1f76af88-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "questionText": "Is Cleveland Clinic concerned about shortages of any medical supplies or medications?", "answerText": "As of March 19th at 11:00 a.m., we have adequate Personal Protective Equipment (PPE).\nWe also have a supply of testing swabs on hand. However, we did not anticipate the impact of the COVID-19 outbreak on Italy, where the swabs are manufactured. We hope to continue to receive additional testing supplies, which will be a key part of our decision-making in the future.\nCleveland Clinic is following Ohio guidelines to postpone non-essential surgeries and procedures. This supports statewide efforts to conserve hospital beds, equipment and supplies.", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://newsroom.clevelandclinic.org/2020/03/18/frequently-asked-questions-about-coronavirus-disease-2019-covid-19/", "sourceName": "Cleveland Clinic", "dateScraped": 1584976955.267069, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1584894600.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "1f76b046-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "answerUUID": "1f76b0f0-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "exampleUUID": "1f76b19a-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "questionText": "Where can I find more information from Cleveland Clinic?", "answerText": "The latest information on COVID-19 can be found on the CDC’s website and at ClevelandClinic.org.", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://newsroom.clevelandclinic.org/2020/03/18/frequently-asked-questions-about-coronavirus-disease-2019-covid-19/", "sourceName": "Cleveland Clinic", "dateScraped": 1584976955.267123, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1584894600.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "1f76b262-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "answerUUID": "1f76b30c-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "exampleUUID": "1f76b3ac-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "questionText": "Is there a hotline I can call for more information on COVID-19?", "answerText": "Cleveland Clinic has a dedicated, 24/7 COVID-19 hotline to answer your questions at 855.697.3750. The Ohio Department of Health also has set up a COVID-19 hotline (1-833-4-ASK-ODH) for those with questions or concerns.\nTravel\nFor the latest information on travel information, alerts and warnings, please visit the CDC’s Coronavirus Disease 2019 Information for Travel website.", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://newsroom.clevelandclinic.org/2020/03/18/frequently-asked-questions-about-coronavirus-disease-2019-covid-19/", "sourceName": "Cleveland Clinic", "dateScraped": 1584976955.267176, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1584894600.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": false, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "1f76b474-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "answerUUID": "1f76b51e-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "exampleUUID": "1f76b5be-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "questionText": "What if my family member traveled from a country or had a layover in a country with widespread or sustained transmission in the last 14 days?", "answerText": "If your family member traveled from or had a layover in a CDC-designated high-risk country in the last 14 days and feels sick with fever, cough or has difficulty breathing, visit Cleveland Clinic Express Care® Online or call or message your primary care physician.\nYour family member should:\nSeek medical care right away. Before they go to a doctor’s office or emergency room, call ahead and tell them about their recent travel and symptoms.\nAvoid contact with others.\nNot travel while sick.\nThey should cover their mouth and nose with a tissue or their sleeve (not their hands) when coughing or sneezing.\nWash hands often with soap and water for 15-20 seconds. Use an alcohol-based hand sanitizer with at least 60% alcohol if soap and water are not available.", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {}}
{"sourceUrl": "https://newsroom.clevelandclinic.org/2020/03/18/frequently-asked-questions-about-coronavirus-disease-2019-covid-19/", "sourceName": "Cleveland Clinic", "dateScraped": 1584976955.2672284, "sourceDate": null, "lastUpdateTime": 1584894600.0, "needUpdate": true, "containsURLs": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "questionUUID": "1f76b67c-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "answerUUID": "1f76b726-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "exampleUUID": "1f76b7c6-6d1a-11ea-bc16-c81f66e17f9e", "questionText": "Should I travel internationally?", "answerText": "CDC provides recommendations on postponing or canceling travel. These are called travel notices and are based on assessment of the potential health risks involved with traveling to a certain area. A list of destinations with travel notices is available at https://www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/2019-ncov/travelers/index.html\n\nAdditional State and National Resources:\nCenters for Disease Control and Prevention\nOhio Department of Health\nFlorida Health\nSouthern Nevada Health District\nAdditional Global Resources:\nWorld Health Organization\nGovernment of Canada\nOntario – Ministry of Health\nPublic Health England\n\nAbout Cleveland Clinic\nCleveland Clinic is a nonprofit multispecialty academic medical center that integrates clinical and hospital care with research and education. Located in Cleveland, Ohio, it was founded in 1921 by four renowned physicians with a vision of providing outstanding patient care based upon the principles of cooperation, compassion and innovation. Cleveland Clinic has pioneered many medical breakthroughs, including coronary artery bypass surgery and the first face transplant in the United States. U.S. News & World Report consistently names Cleveland Clinic as one of the nation’s best hospitals in its annual “America’s Best Hospitals” survey. Among Cleveland Clinic’s 67,554 employees worldwide are more than 4,520 salaried physicians and researchers, and 17,000 registered nurses and advanced practice providers, representing 140 medical specialties and subspecialties. Cleveland Clinic is a 6,026-bed health system that includes a 165-acre main campus near downtown Cleveland, 18 hospitals, more than 220 outpatient facilities, and locations in southeast Florida; Las Vegas, Nevada; Toronto, Canada; Abu Dhabi, UAE; and London, England. In 2019, there were 9.8 million total outpatient visits, 309,000 hospital admissions and observations, and 255,000 surgical cases throughout Cleveland Clinic’s health system. Patients came for treatment from every state and 185 countries. Visit us at clevelandclinic.org. Follow us at twitter.com/CCforMedia and twitter.com/ClevelandClinic. News and resources available at newsroom.clevelandclinic.org.\n Editor’s Note: Cleveland Clinic News Service is available to provide broadcast-quality interviews and B-roll upon request.", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "topic": "", "extraData": {}}
